[
    {
       "question":"Bismillah was called by the name ............  .",
       "choice1":"Master Saheb",
       "choice2": "Magistrate Saheb",
       "choice3": "Doctor Saheb",
       "choice4": "Khan Saheb",
       "answer": 4
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Who was the director of the film called 'Gunj Uthi Shehnai'?",
       "choice1":"Mahesh Bhatt",
       "choice2":"Himesh Reshamia",
       "choice3":"Vijay Bhatt",
       "choice4":"Prakash Mehra",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"Who was the first Indian to greet the nation with his shehnai on 15th August 1947 at Red Fort?",
       "choice1":"Bismillah Khan",
       "choice2": "Ali Bux",
       "choice3": "Amjad Ali Khan",
       "choice4": "Khada Bux",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Tahar Mosiquee ustaad Bismillah Khan auditorium is situated in - ",
       "choice1":"Osaka",
       "choice2":"Behrin",
       "choice3":"Teheran",
       "choice4":"Montreal",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"How many holes did it take him to transform the pungi?",
       "choice1":"Three holes",
       "choice2": "Seven holes",
       "choice3": "Eight holes",
       "choice4": "Nine holes",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Dumraon is a small place in .........",
       "choice1":"Tamil Nadu",
       "choice2":"Bihar",
       "choice3":"Telangana",
       "choice4":"Jharkhand",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"Rasool Bux Khan was ustad Bismillah Khan's -",
       "choice1":"Father",
       "choice2": "Teacher",
       "choice3": "Grand Father",
       "choice4": "Grand grand Father",
       "answer": 3
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Why had the emperor Aurangzeb banned the playing of pungi?",
       "choice1":"Because it had shrill and unpleasant sound.",
       "choice2":"Because it was not as popular as shehnai.",
       "choice3":"Because it did't have seven holes.",
       "choice4":"Because the emperor didn't like it.",
       "answer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":"What gift the little girl stitch for her father ?",
       "choice1":"A pin-cushion",
       "choice2": "Silk scart",
       "choice3": "Silk dress",
       "choice4": "A toy",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Who wrote 'The Little Girl'?",
       "choice1":"Vikram Seth",
       "choice2":"Katherine Mansfield",
       "choice3":"Isaac Asimov",
       "choice4":"V. M. Basheer",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"How many children did the MacDonalds have ?",
       "choice1":"four children",
       "choice2": "five children",
       "choice3": "ten children",
       "choice4": "eight children",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"What type of man Kezia's father was for her ?",
       "choice1":"A figure of fear",
       "choice2":"A figure of love",
       "choice3":"A figure of contrast",
       "choice4":"A figure of purity",
       "answer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":"Kezia was afraid of her .........",
       "choice1":"grandmother",
       "choice2": "father",
       "choice3": "mother",
       "choice4": "Mr. MacDonald",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"What gift did the grandmother suggest Kezia to give her father on his birthday ?",
       "choice1":"a pen ",
       "choice2":"a table-lamp",
       "choice3":"a cigar",
       "choice4":"a pin cushion",
       "answer": 4
   },
   {
       "question":"The cook's name in Kezia's house is - ",
       "choice1":"Alice",
       "choice2": "Bruno",
       "choice3": "Margie",
       "choice4": "Tommy",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Kezia compared her father to a ..........",
       "choice1":"ghost",
       "choice2":"joker",
       "choice3":"giant",
       "choice4":"hermit",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"Kezia's father compared Kezia to - ",
       "choice1": "a brown owl ",
       "choice2": "a white bear",
       "choice3": "a pole bear",
       "choice4": "a golden horse",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Whom did Kezia see in her dream?",
       "choice1":"A robber ",
       "choice2":"A butcher",
       "choice3":"A thief",
       "choice4":"A ghost",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"Who was Kezia ?",
       "choice1":"A little girl",
       "choice2": "Mother",
       "choice3": "Father",
       "choice4": "None of these",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Who was a figure to fear and avoided to the little girl Kezia ?",
       "choice1":"Brother",
       "choice2":"Father",
       "choice3":"Mother",
       "choice4":"Grand Mother",
       "answer": 2
   }
   
   
   
   
   ]